<resources>
    <string name="app_name">UASTS</string>
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_transfers">Transfers</string>
    <string name="title_rumour">Rumour</string>
    <string name="title_standings">Standings</string>
    <string name="title_profil">Profil</string>

    <string-array name="positions_array">
        <item>GK</item>
        <item>CB</item>
        <item>RB</item>
        <item>LB</item>
        <item>DM</item>
        <item>CM</item>
        <item>AM</item>
        <item>RM</item>
        <item>LM</item>
        <item>RW</item>
        <item>LW</item>
        <item>ST</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="description_templates">
        <item>The transfer grapevine is abuzz with whispers surrounding the potential move of [Player Name] to [Club Name]. Speculations are ripe, hinting at a substantial transfer fee hovering around [Transfer Fee]. Fans are eagerly anticipating further developments in this saga! #TransferGossip #StayTuned</item>
        <item>Recent reports have ignited talks of [Player Name] being on the radar of [Club Name] as they look to bolster their squad. Sources suggest that negotiations are underway, with the proposed transfer fee estimated to be in the region of [Transfer Fee]. Keep your eyes peeled for more updates! #TransferRumors #WatchOut</item>
        <item>Rumblings in the transfer market suggest that discussions are heating up between [Player Name] and [New Club Name]. While the exact figures remain undisclosed, speculation is rife that the potential transfer fee could surpass [Transfer Fee]. Will this murmuring transform into a concrete deal? #TransferTalk #RumorMill</item>
        <item>Excitement mounts among supporters as rumors circulate about [Club Name] expressing a keen interest in securing the services of [Player Name]. Sources indicate that talks have progressed, with murmurs hinting at a transfer fee exceeding [Transfer Fee]. An intriguing narrative unfolds! #TransferSpeculation #FootballGossip</item>
        <item>The transfer rumor mill goes into overdrive as reports emerge of [Club Name] intensifying their pursuit of [Player Name]. While details remain sketchy, whispers in the wind suggest a potential transfer fee close to [Transfer Fee]. Will these whispers culminate in a significant transfer deal? Stay tuned for more updates! #TransferRumor #StayUpdated</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>